Tap, tap— a rhythm pops in my heart
Spinning round, sweet parade
A little smile spreads, yeah
I dance in the neon, babe
Perked-up ears, sparkles pop
At my toes, swing-swing hop
Your eyes flash— "Dding!"
Should I tease you today…? Hehe
La la la— come follow me
On top of a sparkling beat
Just one little glitch
Sweetly swaying, look now…
Hey, hey!
Kawaii rhythm wraps around me
It's a sweetly bouncing bounce
Boop-boop! My heart jumps
It sparkles with a "pop!" at your fingertips
Swing me round and round tonight
A sparkling club delight
A pounding noise inside
Your and my cute collide
Swing me round and round tonight
A sparkling club delight
A pounding noise inside
Your and my cute collide
Click— a smile inside the camera
Your warmth softly reaches me
When you say, "One, two, three," yeah
Our very own little gala
Tap-tap-tap— no need for words
The rhythm will tell us everything
A night like sparkling candy
This feeling, keep holding me tight
Nya! Follow me, sparkling—
A starlight-spraying swing attack
Sweet enough to make me dizzy
Our very own secret track
Hey, hey!
Kawaii rhythm wraps around me
It's a sweetly bouncing bounce
Boop-boop! My heart jumps
It sparkles with a "pop!" at your fingertips
Swing me round and round tonight
A sparkling club delight
A pounding noise inside
Your and my cute collide
Swing me round and round tonight
A sparkling club delight
A pounding noise inside
Your and my cute collide